Hi, my name is Sue Conrad, and I am going to show you how to exercise in your car.
You may think it sounds kind of silly to do exercises in your car, but we spend a lot of time in our car, and this will help reduce some of the tension and stress that we spend driving around town.
The first exercise we're going to do is a shoulder shrug.
You want to take your shoulders and bring them up towards your ears, you're going to hold two or three seconds, then you're going to relax.
So basically you're tensing up your shoulders and then you're releasing, all the stress coming out of your shoulders.
I would suggest doing this eight to ten times holding for two to three seconds, and if you feel like you want to do some more you can do another set or two.
Another exercise you can do to keep your tush from getting numb is to tense your gluteal muscles, hold for ten seconds and then release.
So you're going to tense, release, tense, and release.
Another exercise you can do is to help strengthen the inner thighs.
You can either take a small pillow, a towel, or a sweatshirt, whatever you have in your vehicle, put in between your thighs and you can squeeze your inner thighs and then relax.
So you're going to tense those inner thigh muscles, and you're going to release.
Another exercise you can do in your vehicle to help loosen up the shins are toe raises.
You can bring your toes forward, hold for ten seconds, and then relax.
Bring your toes forward raising the heels, holding for ten seconds, and then release.
And that's how you can exercise in your car!